You're really going out in that?
お前　本当にその格好でいくのか
I've told you before that a true heir
of the Night Tribe transcends heat.
真祖たる我は暑さをも凌駕しておると言っておろう
今日は一段とすげえなあ
Even hotter today...
Abominable light of the sun...
忌まわしき太陽の光め　ククク
You may look forward to the day the
Night Tribe plunges the world into darkness.
いずれ　我ら夜の血族が世界を闇に包み込む日を
楽しみにしているがよい
Right now, I wouldn't object to that...
そんな日が来るといいな
WANAWANA
QUIVER
Vigorously bursting with goodness
グッと Good 弾ける
You know, that's surprisingly addicting
案外なんだい ハマってんじゃん
Let's get the ball rolling
while you're idly acting shy!
人見知りしてる暇に 始めよう
Let's make friends and play, yeah!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
"Haganai"
クールに見えて 実は超寂しい
I look cool, but I'm actually super lonely
(My delusions went bye, bye, bye
Best friends are a nope, nope, nope, nope)
妄想ならバイバイバイ
親友なら いないいないいないいない
I'm not held back any, but this isn't enough
何不自由なく だけど足りない
(Is a happy life in the real world far, far, far away?
Best friends are a nope, nope, nope, nope)
リア充から遠い遠い遠い
親友なら いないいないいないいない
If a group of unlucky people gathered together,
残念同士で 集まったら
Ah... I can't picture it
Ah- 予想が出来ない 展開の 地雷を踏んだ
This situation is like stepping on a mine!
FIDGET
SOWASOWA
絶対絶対覗きたい
I totally, totally want to take a peek
I don't want to regret this 100 times
後悔100回したくないって
Totally toss aside and
shake off that boring pride
つまんない プライドなんて
捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Unfortunately, this idea popped into my mind,
and you know, it's surprisingly addicting
残念観念してみたら
案外なんだいハマってんじゃん
Let's find some as we
clash and rattle each other!
ぶつかって どぎまぎ合って 見つけよう
Let's make friends and play, yeah!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
I totally, totally want to take a peek
絶対絶対覗きたい
You! Toss aside and shake yourself off
YOU！ 捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Yes! Well? What do you think of that?
Yes！ どーだいどーだいそこんとこ
本字幕由诸神卖萌组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神卖萌组---
日听：apollius   翻译: 银苹果   校对：喵儿 小草爱吃梨
时间轴：nono   后期：Maize
"My Cell Phone Doesn't Get Many Calls"
はあ　生き返る
I'm alive again...
あにき
Aniki...
You must be exhausted.
お疲れさまです
So you finally made it, Kodaka?
やっと来たか　小鷹
The same time we always
meet after school, right?
いつも放課後に来てる時間だろう
It's summer vacation, so what would
be the point of meeting at the usual time?
夏休みなのに　いつもと同じような時間に来てどうする
When did you guys get here?
お前らはいつ来たんだ
About 100.
１時くらいだ
When I got here, Meat
was already playing a game.
私が来たときには肉がゲームをやっていた
Sena got here a little before Yozora.
星奈の姉御は夜空の姉御の少し前に
Everyone's so early...
みんな早いんだなあ　幸村は
How about you, Yukimura?
I was here at 8:00.
わたくしは８時です
If I were ever here later than you, Aniki,
I would have to commit seppuku, so...
万一あにきに遅れるようなことあらば　切腹ものですゆえ
I don't think you should be
prepared to do that over a club...
そんな覚悟で部活に来られても
This is your meal for today, Aniki.
本日のお食事です　あにき
Well, actually, I had lunch at home...
いや　家で昼飯食ってきたし
And you don't have to fix me
snacks even during summer break.
てゆーか　夏休みまで食事用意しなくていいって
Does this mean you're relieving me of my post?
それは　お役御免ということですか
Aniki doesn't need me anymore...
私は　あにきにとって不要な存在
Since it's come to this, I will meet
my end by committing seppuku.
斯くなる上は　切腹して果てる所存
Wait, I need you! I couldn't do without you!
待て…必要　お前　超必要だから
Hey, hey! Brother, you're not gonna eat that?
なあなあ　お兄ちゃんそれいらないのか
I see...
そうか　こいつ俺の弁当を待ってたのか
She was waiting for me to bring her lunch...
Um, Yukimura. Is it okay if
I give the pastries to Maria?
ああ幸村　このパンマリアにやってもいいか
I mean, I'd be grateful if
you prepared lunch for Maria,
てゆーか　夏休みの間
俺の代わりにマリアの昼飯を用意してくれるとありがたいんだが
instead of me, during summer vacation.
It's improper for a samurai
to serve two masters.
二君に仕えるなど　もののふにあるまじきこと
This guy's a pain in the ass...
めんどくさいやつだなあ
Yukimura! Maria is, um...
幸村　マリアはええと 俺の妹みたいなものだ
She's like my little sister.
It's not especially improper
主君の妹の面倒を見るのは　別にもののふにあるまじくないだろ
for a samurai to look after the
little sister of his master, is it?
True... I mean...
確かに　いえ
That would actually be a great honor!
それどころか大変に名誉なこと
Little sister?
妹　お兄ちゃんの妹
Brother's little sister?
Maria-dono...
マリア殿　あにきの命により
In accordance with Aniki's command,
from today on, I will be in
charge of preparing your meals.
本日よりわたくしがお食事係をお務めいたします
I'm counting on you!
よきにはからえ
おお　これがコンビニのパンか
So these are convenience store pastries?!
わあ　添加物すげえ
Look at all the additives in here!
Deeelicious!
うまーい！
This looks incredibly unhealthy!
めちゃくちゃ健康に悪そうだなこれ
A real man isn't bothered by additives.
真の男たるもの　添加物など気にしてはならないのです
Yukimura, from tomorrow on,
only bring healthy stuff for Maria.
幸村　明日からマリアには健康に良さそうなものをやるようにしてくれ
Understood, Aniki.
分かりました　あにき
If you give your dog a taste of luxury,
disciplining it becomes a major pain.
飼い犬に贅沢の味を覚えさせると
しつけが面倒だぞ
Well, I'll see you later.
じゃあ　行ってくるからな
God, it's hot...
ああ　暑い
You're working as hard as ever, Aniki.
おつとめお疲れさまです　あにき
Where are the others?
ほかのやつらは
The girls aren't here yet.
姉御達はまだです
Maria-dono remembered a duty she
had to do as a sister and went home.
マリア殿は　シスターとしてのお役目を思い出して
お帰りになりました
I see.
そっか
Did you give Maria lunch?
マリアに　ご飯は
Yes. Just as you instructed,
I was careful to make it healthy.
はい
お指図のとおり　健康にも気を使い 栄養があるものを
Something nutritious...
Protein?
プロテイン
Did Maria eat all that?!
マリア　これ全部食ったのか
It was your order, Aniki, so I hardened
my heart and forced her to eat it.
あにきのご命令でしたので
心を鬼にして力ずくで食べていただきました
Seriously?
マジでか
Now I understand how Hashiba Hideyoshi
felt when he executed Manpukumaru.
わたくし　万福丸を処刑した羽柴秀吉の気持ちが分かりました
Manpukumaru?
[manpuku: full stomach]
万福丸
He was the eldest son of Azai Nagamasa,
who was overthrown by Oda Nobunaga.
織田信長に滅ぼされた　浅井長政の嫡男で
わずか１０歳で磔に処されたのです
But he was crucified at the tender age of ten.
I'm sure that when Manpukumaru met
his end, he screamed just like she did today.
きっとそのとき　万福丸もあのように泣き叫んだことでしょう
Screamed?!
泣き叫んだって　あのように？
Just like she did?!
Maria-dono remembered a duty she
had to do as a sister and went home.
シスターとしてのお役目を思い出して　お帰りに
Remembered... Remembered...
思い出して…　思い出して…
F-From tomorrow on, please make it something
明日からは
マリアがおいしく食べられて　添加物の少ないものを頼む
that tastes good and is low in additives.
I don't want her going through
Manpukumaru's tragedy again!
万福丸の悲劇を繰り返してはならない
Understood. Please leave it to me.
はい　お任せください
So no one's coming after all...
結局　誰も来ねえ
You're working hard, Aniki.
お疲れさまでした　あにき
Hey, everyone...
お前らなあ
Why didn't any of you come yesterday?
昨日なんで誰も来なかったんだよ？
Kodaka-sempai! Were you lonely
because you couldn't meet Rika?
小鷹先輩　理科に会えなくて寂しかったんですか
It's not like I was particularly lonely, but...
別に寂しかったわけじゃないけど
ふん　昨日は用事があったのだ
I had something to do yesterday.
I had a hard time yesterday, too.
あたしも昨日は大変だったのよ
A hard time?
大変
The game was almost over,
もうすぐ終わりだし　エンディング見てから行こうと思ってたら
so I thought I'd come here
as soon as I saw the ending...
...but then it actually took
me about four more hours!
なんとそこから４時間ぐらいあったのよね　予想外
Longer than I expected!
まあ　すごく感動したからいいけど
But I was really moved, so I don't mind...
I mean, when Mikane
reaches the goal, it's so touching!
もうね　美鐘がゴールするときなんて本当に
So you were playing a game...
ゲームの話かよ
I'll lend it to you! Play it, too, Kodaka!
貸したげるから　小鷹もやりなさいよ
It'll be a missed opportunity if you don't!
やらないのは人生を損してるわ
After you see the ending, if you
start over again from the beginning,
エンディングを見た後に　もう一回最初から始めると
it ties in with the last scene...
ラストシーンとの繋がりが分かって　より感っ
と…ところで
B-By the way!
What?
何よ
I think we should do something
部室に集まる時間とか
so we all know what time we're
meeting here and who can't make it.
みんなの出欠が分かるようにしておいた方がいいと思うんだ
You may have something there...
それはそうかもしれないな
That's not a bad idea coming from you, Kodaka.
小鷹にしてはいいこと言うじゃない
So how do we do it?
で　具体的にはどうするの
Um... a Net bulletin board?
ええと　ネットの掲示板使うのは
- Forget it!
- No way!
却下だ（いやだ）
A flat-out no?! Why?!
即答　何で
Other than for mail orders
and researching things,
私は通販と調べもの以外では
I try to use the Net as little as possible.
なるべくネットを使わない主義なのだ
Oh, really?
そうなのか
Yes. Recently.
最近はそうなのだ
I did something last time...
以前　ちょっとやらかしてな
I'm not even gonna ask what it was.
何をかは聞かないでおこう
Thank you.
ありがとう
I've had a bad experience with Net
bulletin boards too, so I don't wanna use one.
あたしもネット掲示板には　嫌な思い出があるから使いたくないよね
ああ　思い出したらムカついてきた
Just remembering it ticks me off!
The way those trolls treated me!
あいつら　あたしを荒らし扱いして
あいつら絶対に許さない
I'll never forgive them!
Did you get in an argument?
口論でもしたのか
After all, those morons were
calling my Natsumi a hot-blooded idiot!
だって　あのバカども
あたしの夏美を脳筋の体力バカよばわりしてたのよ
許せるわけないじゃない
I couldn't just let that slide!
Despite the way she looks,
Natsumi has a pretty sensitive side.
夏美はね　ああ見えて結構繊細なところもあるのよ
Despite the way she looks?
ああ見えてって言われても
Badmouthing Natsumi in front
of me is a declaration of war!
あたしの前で夏美の悪口を言ったら
それは宣戦布告でしょうが
Either they admit how
stupid they are and apologize,
あいつらが自分のバカさ加減を認めて謝るか
それか滅びるまで戦うしかないじゃないの
or we fight until one side is decimated!
Anyway, bulletin boards
are no good for you, right?
とにかく掲示板は駄目ってことだな
Then how about that, you know, SNS
thing that's popular these days, like Nixi?
じゃあ　あれは最近はやりのSNSだっけか
ほら　nixi
え　小鷹nixiやってるの
You use Nixi, Kodaka?
In that case, invite me!
だったら招待してよ
いや　俺はやってないけど
No, I don't use it... and I'm
guessing you don't either, Sena.
星奈もか
Nope.
How about you, Yozora?
夜空は
私が会員になれるわけがないだろう
There's no way I could become a member.
Me neither.
わたくしもです
Rika isn't a member either!
理科も入ってないですね
Basically, if a real friend
doesn't invite you, you can't join.
あれって　基本的にはリアルの友達が招待してくれないと入れませんから
We can't even join Nixi?
俺達は　nixiに入会すらできないのか
But... Nixi isn't the only
social networking service!
いやでも　SNSはnixiだけじゃない
There are lots where
you don't need an invitation.
今は　招待制じゃないのもいっぱいあるんだろう
Um, Kodaka-sempai...
あの　小鷹先輩
Can't we just keep in touch
with each other using our cells?
普通に携帯で連絡を取り合うんじゃ駄目なんですか
Cells?!
携帯　それはもしかして携帯電話のことか
Do you mean "cell phones"?
Uh huh...
そうですけど
That's right. I can use my cell phone
to do more than just call home...
そうか　携帯電話を家に連絡する以外で使うとか
Rika, you're a genius!
理科　お前天才だな
Certainly, that never crossed my mind.
確かに　その発想はなかった
I suppose my cell phone isn't
just a tool to look for karaoke shops!
携帯電話は　カラオケ屋を探すためだけの道具ではなかったのか
Shiguma Rika... I have no choice
but to acknowledge you as a genius!
志熊理科　貴様を天才だと認めざるを得ないようだな
Rika is happy to be praised.
褒めてもらえて嬉しいです
Then should we start by
exchanging our email addresses?
じゃあ　とりあえず アドレスの交換しちゃいます
Yeah!
Th-This is it!
こ…これだ
"7/19: House"
"7/17: House"
"7/14: Kobato"
"7/10: Kobato"
M-Me too!
わ…私も
Here it is!
あった
I took my cell phone out!
携帯電話を出したぞ
Then let's go ahead and exchange addresses.
じゃあ　アドレスの交換しちゃいましょう
Right...
そうだな
What a brightly colored
phone you have, Kodaka-sempai!
小鷹先輩の携帯 すごい色ですね
Rika doesn't often see them like that.
そうそう見ませんよ
えっ　そうか
Really?
Okay, let's do it with infrared light.
じゃあ　赤外線お願いします
I-Infrared light?
せ…赤外線
W-Why infrared light?
何だよ赤外線って
Certainly, I think I've heard
the legend that it's possible
確かにに　最近の携帯電話は赤外線でデータのやり取りが可能だ
for recent cell phones to
exchange data with infrared light,
という伝説を聞いたことがあるような気がするが
but it's actually true?
実話だったのか
W-What do I push?
ど…どれだ？
マジかよ
Are you serious?! When did
cell phones evolve like that?!
いつの間にそんな進化したんだ　携帯電話
There.
どうぞ
Y-Yukimura?
ゆ…幸村
あ　どうもです幸村君
Thank you, Yukimura-kun!
"Infrared Communication"
"Opening Kusunoki Yukimura's
message. Record in telephone book?"
はい　幸村君のアドレスゲット
Okay, Rika got your address, Yukimura-kun!
"Received"
"All Data Received"
"Sent"
こちらも確認できました
I've received yours, as well.
D-Don't tell me they're
already done exchanging data?!
まさか今ので　データの交換が終わったのか
In that short space of time?!
あんな短時間で
Hey, modern kids really are
different from the rest of us...
おいおい　さすが現代っ子は違うな
It can do all that?!
マジパネェよ
Yeah. This is the virtual generation
that lives in a digital world.
これがデジタルな世界に生きるバーチャル世代
- To them, everything is like a video game.
- They sure are going on about being
different than us in just one regard...
やつらにとっては全てがゲーム感覚だということが
理科達と一コしか違わないのにめちゃくちゃ言ってますよね
- Those kids don't know what pain is.
- They sure are going on about being
different than us in just one regard...
- When I think that this generation
is going to bear the responsibility...
- People like Aniki, who survive by relying on their
own strength, have no interest in cell phones, right?
あにきのように　己の力のみを頼みとして生きるお方は
携帯になど関心がないのですね
...of the future of Japan,
everything goes dark before my eyes...
- People like Aniki, who survive by relying on their
own strength, have no interest in cell phones, right?
I didn't think you'd be able to handle
infrared without any trouble, Yukimura!
ていうか　お前が普通に赤外線を使いこなすとは思わなかったぞ　幸村
Oh...
I just don't know how to do it!
やっぱり分からん
It's strange for someone who has no friends
こんな機能　友達がいない人間が使える方がおかしいのだ
to be able to use a function like this!
Kodaka! I'll type in your address
the normal way, so tell me what it is!
小鷹　普通に登録するからアドレスを教えろ
Got it! I was just thinking
it'd be faster that way too.
分かった　俺もその方が早いと思ってたところだ
Here, this is my number and address.
ほら　これが俺の番号とアドレスだ
I went too far...
あ　行きすぎた
Still, your address is too complicated...
しかし　ややこしいアドレスだな
It's because I haven't changed
it since I bought the phone.
あ　初めて買ったときから変更してないからな
うん　点はどこだ　点…
Where's the dot?
ふう　できた
I did it!
Good.
A-All right... Kodaka, I'm gonna...
よ…よし
では　送るぞ小鷹
...send you an email...
email from a cell phone...
メールを　携帯電話でメールを
Y-Yeah...
お…おう
I got it!
届いた
届いたか
You got it?!
"Email"
This is your email, Yozora?
これが夜空のメールか
Let's see, to register it...
ええと　たしか登録は
"Mika... zuki... Yo... zora..."
みかつき　よる…そら
初めての家族以外のアドレスだ
This is my first email
address from outside my family!
It feels like something is filling up my heart!
なんかこう 胸に込み上げてくるものがあるな
Oh, really?
そうだったのか
You didn't have addresses of
kids from your previous schools?
前の学校の連中のアドレスとかは
No.
入ってない
At my farewell parties, there were
people who said they'd send me emails,
お別れ会のとき「メール送るから」って言ってくれたやつはいたけど
よく考えたらアドレス交換したことがなかった
but when I think about it, I never
did exchange addresses with them.
I see. Then my address is your
first one, apart from your family...
そうか
私のアドレスが家族以外で初めてか
Incidentally, my phone doesn't
even have my family's addresses saved.
ちなみに私のなんて　家族のアドレスすら入ってないぞ
Your address is my genuine first one, Kodaka!
小鷹が正真正銘の一人目だ
Wow, really?!
そうか
Maybe we should have taught them
how to use infrared data transfer,
赤外線通信のやり方ぐらい教えてあげてもよかったのですが
but looking at those two in such high spirits
はしゃいでる先輩達を見ていると
makes Rika feel that we who
know how to do it are the losers.
理科達の方が負けた気になります
Hmph!
ふん
Fussing over a cell phone! It's stupid!
たかが携帯電話くらいでバッカみたい
What are you mad about?
何怒ってるんだ
怒ってないわよ
I'm not mad!
Well, okay then...
ならいいけど
Come on, tell me your address, too.
ほら　お前のアドレスも教えてくれよ
Don't have one.
…てない
持ってないわよ　携帯電話なんて
I don't have a stupid cell phone!
Oh, really?
そうだったのか
It's not like I'm envious or anything!
別に羨ましくなんてないわよ
They're gadgets made for the
giggling airheads in my class!
あんなの　クラスでいつもギャハハって笑ってるバカ女の持ち物なのよ
It's unnecessary for someone
with as much class as me!
あたしみたいな高貴な人間には必要ないの
Well, there are a lot of people around
the world who don't need a cell phone.
まあ　携帯必要ないってやつも世の中には結構いるよな
That's right.
そのとおりよ
I don't need a phone, let alone a cell phone!
携帯どころか電話すら必要ないわ
No matter where I am or what I'm doing,
どこにいても何をしていても　愚民どもは
the ignorant masses should gratefully
listen to this goddess's heavenly voice!
神である私の天の声をありがたく受け取るべきなのよ
That's asking too much...
いや　それは無茶だろう
Hello?
はい
It's me.
私だ
Save my phone number.
私の番号を登録しておけ
Okay, sure.
あ　分かった
Wait. As long as we're
on the phone, let's talk.
待て　せっかくだから電話でしゃべろう
えっ　まあいいけど
Well, okay, but...
では　昨日の夕飯の話でもするか
All right, why don't we
talk about last night's dinner?
What did you eat, Kodaka?
小鷹は何を食べたのだ
Um... What was it, again?
ええと何だっけ
Who cares about what you
two had for dinner last night?!
あんたらねえ
昨日のご飯の話なんかどうでもいいでしょうが
Quiet, Meat.
うるさいぞ肉
Can't you keep your mouth shut
when people are talking on the phone?
貴様は電話中に静かにしていることもできないのか
まったく非常識な肉だな
You really are meat lacking any common sense.
Anyway, cell phones are convenient, aren't they?
しかし便利だな
携帯電話というものは
離れていても会話ができる
We can have a conversation
even when we're apart.
In that case, go away and
then have a conversation!
だったら離れたところで会話しなさいよ
I'll give you a call on your cell
when I'm leaving for the club.
部活に出かけるときは携帯に連絡を入れる
And from now on, let's plan all
our club activities together by email.
あと　これからの活動予定をみんなでメールで相談したりしよう
ところで　昨日の夕飯だが
By the way, I went to a restaurant
for dinner last night and had
私はお店で「肉」を食べたぞ
meat.
To be precise, it was curry with chicken
正確には　鶏「肉」の入ったカレーなのだが
meat
in it, but the
「肉」が　とても軟らかくておいしかった
meat
was so tender and delicious.
What are you talking about?
何を話してるのよ
Meat,
「肉」には関係のないことだ
it has nothing to do with you.
That restaurant's meat wasn't just chicken meat.
その店の「肉」は　鶏「肉」だけでなく
They also had pig meat and cow meat,
all of which were domestic products.
豚「肉」や牛「肉」も　全て国産にこだわっているのだが
It was so delicious and yet reasonably
priced, I wondered how they could
値段をギリギリまで安くしているのが心「にく」い
meet the demand.
You could eat all the
meat you wanted for just...
298で　あれだけ食べられ…
Shut up with your "Meat! Meat!"
にくにく　うるさーい
Hey!
Stupid! Stupid! Idiot!
バーカバーカ　アホー
Yozora, you're an idiot!
夜空のアホー
Dammit, that stupid Meat...
くそ　あのバカ肉め
You really do have a talent for getting
under Sena's skin with pinpoint accuracy.
お前は本当にピンポイントで星奈の嫌がることをするのが得意だよな
ただいま
I'm home.
遅かったな　我が半身よ
You're late, my other half.
Yeah. I'll go make dinner now.
ああ　今夕飯作るからな
In one stroke, my contact addresses double!
連絡先が一気に倍に
Who would be calling at this hour?
何なんだよ　こんな時間に
Hello? Hasegawa here...
はい　羽瀬川ですけど
H-Hello?!
も…もしもし
What the hell? A crank call?
なんだよ　イタ電か
Hello?
Hello?!
U-Um, I'm Kashiwazaki Sena...
あの…　わ…わたくし柏崎星奈ですけど
I-I-I-I-Is Kodaka...
I mean, Kodaka-kun... there?
こ…小鷹っ　えっと…小鷹君いますか？
星奈
Sena?
Huh? Is this Kodaka?
あれ　もしかして小鷹
Yeah.
おう
Stupid! You dummy! Don't scare me, stupid!
バカッ　もうバカ
びっくりさせるんじゃないわよバカ
Your voice is scary, moron!
あんたの声怖いのよ　バカ
つーか　お前な
Look, what the hell time do you think it is?
今何時だと思ってんだ
Enough about that. Kodaka,
what's your cell phone like?
ねえねえ　そんなことより小鷹
あんたの携帯って　どんなの
What's it like? It's a normal one.
どんなのって　普通だけど
But there are all kinds, aren't there?!
だーかーらー
なんかあるじゃない　色々
Like companies and models...
会社とか機種とか
The company is Turn-AU.
会社は　∀Ｕ
I don't really know what model it is...
機種は　よく分からん
Look it up now!
すぐに調べて
Huh?
Just do it!
いいから
Um, it's an M61b...
えーと　M61bってやつ
Turn-AU M61b, right?
∀Ｕの　M61bね
Yeah.
うん分かった　それじゃあね
Got it. Talk to you later.
What the hell was that about?
何なんだ　いったい
"Waiting for you here
totally naked, Kodaka-sempai.
「小鷹先輩が来るのを全裸で待っています
あ　今理科のヌード想像したでしょ
You just imagined Rika in the nude, didn't you?
You have a dirty mind, Sempai!"
先輩のエッチ」
"Shiguma"
"Subject: Butt"
"Incidentally, Yozora-sempai
is in her birthday suit, too!
「ちなみに　夜空先輩も今全裸ですよ
As proof, I'm sending you a
photo of Sempai's cute, perky tushy!"
証拠に　先輩のプリンとしたかわいらしいお尻の写真を送りますね」
"That was Rika's arm!"
「さっきの理科のは　理科の腕だぞ」
"Ohhh!"
「いやん」
「えッ　夜空先輩
"Yozora-sempai, why are you
pulling down Rika's panties?
どうして理科のパンツを脱がすのですか
Aieee! I can't pose like
this, it's too embarrassing!"
やあん　そんな恥ずかしい格好できません　ああ～ッ」
Kodaka, be careful.
小鷹気をつけろ　こいつ変態だ
This one's a pervert!
Kodaka-sempai!
小鷹先輩
Rika's just noticed how great
the girls' love genre is, too!
理科さっき百合もいけることに気づきました
Rika thinks that as long as
it's erotic, it's probably all good!
たぶん理科　エロければなんでもいんだと思います
You really have a lot of energy, huh?
お前は本当に元気だよな
It's only tea, but...
粗茶ですが
Thank you.
サンキュー
Where is everyone?
みんなは
They all had things to do, so they went home.
用事があるって帰ったぞ
Why don't we take off too?
そろそろ俺達も帰るか
Yeah...
The goddess has descended to Earth!
女神が降臨しに来たわよ
Okay.
I'm going back to sleep.
また寝る
W-What's with the lack of reactions?!
な…何なのよ　この無反応ぶりは
I wonder if you'll be able keep up
the indifference when you see this!
これを見てもまだそんな反応ができるかしらね
ふふ　どう
What do you think? I asked Daddy for
it yesterday, so he bought one for me!
昨日　パパに頼んだら
買ってくれることになったの
Huh? That's the same one as mine.
あれ　それ俺のと同じだな
色まで
Even the color...
H-Huh. Go figure. W-What a coincidence.
へえ　そうなんだ　き…奇遇ね
It's no coincidence...
いや　奇遇も何も
The same as Kodaka's?
小鷹のと同じ
Now we can exchange addresses!
というわけでアドレス交換するわよ
Hurry up!
早く　早く
All right...
Do you know how to do infrared data transfer?
赤外線通信のやり方は分かるか
Of course!
当然よ
小鷹こそ　昨日覚えたばっかのくせに
You just learned how to do
it yourself yesterday, Kodaka!
That's true...
まあな
Come on! I'll do you a favor and
exchange addresses with you too, Yozora!
夜空も交換してあげるわよ
I don't need your address.
私は貴様のアドレスなどをいらん
Hey! I went to the trouble of buying this,
せっかく買ったんだから教えてくれでもいいじゃない
so the least you could
do is tell me your address!
Do you want me to
share it with you that badly?
そんなに教えてほしいのか
N-No, it's not like that...
べ…別にそういうわけじゃないけど
あんたのアドレスなんて
I have no interest in your address at all.
全然知りたくもなんともないけど
I'm just saying that, as clubmates,
同じ部活のよしみで　仕方なくアドレス交換してやろうって言ってるのよ
I thought I'd do you a favor by
exchanging addresses with you.
感謝しなさいよね
Be grateful!
そうか　ありがとう
I see. Thank you! I'll just
accept the feeling behind it.
気持ちだけ受け取っておこう
Just the feeling isn't good enough!
気持ちだけじゃ駄目なんだってば
Bitch with a greedy-looking face...
物欲しそうな顔をしてこのアバズレめ
そんなに欲しいなら誠意を見せてみろ
If you want it that badly,
show me your sincerity.
Sincerity?! I'm not gonna
lick your feet or anything!
誠意って
足なんて舐めないんだからね
Oh, just forget it! Stupid Yozora!
もういいわよ　夜空のバカ
She's too soft.
歯ごたえがなかったな
"Kashiwazaki Sena"
星奈だ
It's Sena.
"I'm gonna harass the moron by email,
so sneak me over Yozora's address."
「バカに嫌がらせのメールを送ってやるから
こっそり夜空のアドレス教えてよ」
This is her first email?
初めてのメールがこれかよ
That stupid Meat...
あのバカ肉め
Kodaka, show me Meat's address.
小鷹　肉のアドレスを見せろ
There's nothing for it.
I'll send Meat my address.
仕方ないから　私から肉にアドレスを教えてやるとしよう
O-Okay...
"Neighbors Club"
何よ　何なのよ
What?! What is this?!
Tell me, what is this?!
ねえ　何なの
It won't stop! W-What should I do?!
止まらないの　どうすれば
What is this?!
何だ　これ
My cell phone...
私の携帯
Well, I'm going home.
さあ帰るぞ
助けてよ　小鷹！
Help me, Kodaka!
S-Sure, let me see it.
ああ　貸してみろ
W-What'll I do if it can't be fixed?
直らなかったらどうしよう
My cell phone...
私の携帯
No, I think it'll be okay.
いや　たぶん大丈夫だよ
泣くな　ほら
Look, see? I'll fix it.
ちゃんと直るって　壊れてないよ
It's not broken, Sena.
Ah, my mind is escaping
reality as ideally as imaginable
あー 脳內 想像理想の 現実逃避
今更どっちだっていっけど 友達作り
Not that it really matters
now if I... make friends
一人寂しい奴だと蔑む 視線が気になる
Those eyes that belittle me saying,
"You're a lonesome person on your own," bug me
So, while I was thinking that it'd be cool...
で 上っ面だけ集まったら
それでいいと 思っているうちに
...if only a superficial group gathered up,
They show up, one here,
one there, and gather together
あれよあれよと登場 揃って 破天荒な奴らに
The unique characters
Throw me off balance
マイペース 乱されてゆく 頭くる！特に憎っくき肉
It ticks me off! Especially that mean meat!
My chest is secretly filled with
apprehension and I feel a bit indecisive
私の胸秘かに焦って 優柔不斷気味で
I can't tell you what's in my heart
My heart 伝えられない 殘念なのは 私なのか
Am I the one disappointed by that?
Plow through the fog today!
もやもやを かきわけ Today！
Ever since the day I got left behind,
my maiden heart has been filled with regret
置き去りにされた 乙女心 あの日から悔やんでいる
Hurry and find it...my lost heart
早く見つけ出して 迷子のココロ
"Turn-AU Shop"
"Sea God's Palace Land"
Meat, these days, everyone has a smart phone.
肉　最近時代はスマートフォンらしい
Smart phone?
スマートフォン　き…聞いたことあるわ
I-I've heard of them!
高性能で何でもできるが使うには条件がある
They're efficient and can do anything,
but there's a condition to use them.
You have to be smart, Meat,
so naturally, that rules you out.
スマートというくらいだから
当然肉　お前は使えない
えっ　本当に
Really?!
ウソだ　お前は本当にバカだな
I'm lying.
You really are stupid!
な…何よ　一瞬信じちゃったじゃない
W-What?! I believed you for a second there!
ククク　ご苦労
考えたらこの女神に使えないものなんてありえないし
But now that I think about it, there couldn't
possibly be anything that this
goddess couldn't use. In the first...
だいたい
次回「スクール水着は出番がない」
Next time: "School Swimsuits Don't Appear."
"Next time: School Swimsuits Don't Appear"
えっ　水着回
A swimsuit episode?
Yeesh! Why are men so hooked on swimsuits?!
まったく男ときたらすぐ水着なんぞに釣られおって